Guide to the Cornell Information Technologies records,1940-2009.
Cornell Information Technologies Records
- Magazines, Articles, etc on Technology, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- Supercomputing, RISC Tech, Software, CMOS Tech, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- Programming Languages/Applications Technology in 1990s, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- Cornell Applications, Reports and Miscellany, 1990 (Box 54)
- Magnetic Tape and Disk Technologies, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- Telecommunications Act of 1996, 1996 (Box 54)
- Materials for the 1990s Introduction, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- 1990 Intro (technical information), 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- Finishing 1990s - Technical Overview, 1990-1999 (Box 54)
- IR Enterprise Team - Meetings, plans, emails, 1994-1995 (Box 54)
- IR Enterprise Team - Meetings, plans, emails, 1993-1994 (Box 54)
- Design Options for Developing WWW apps, 1995 (Box 54)
  Mandarin Project and Information Access Project
- Central Heating Plant - CHIPS Information System, 1991-1992 (Box 54)
- Just the Facts and Mandarin related issues and items, 1991-1992 (Box 54)
- Just the Facts - Development with Highlights and Statistics, 1991-1992 (Box 54)
- Bear Facts - Student Access and Personal Information, 1991 (Box 54)
- Document Imaging Studies - Peter DeLorme and others, 1995 (Box 54)
- Johnson Museum - Automating Collection Records, 1990 (Box 54)
- ADSPAC - emails, Minutes and Support Materials, 1994-1996 (Box 54)
- ADSPAC Planning Retreats, Re-engineering, 1995 (Box 54)
- Emails from STOP/IAP and Data Warehousing, 1993-1996 (Box 54)
- Emails - PeopleSoft, 1994-1997 (Box 54)
- Emails - Project 2000, 1994-1996 (Box 54)
- ADSPAC Project Priority Process, 1992 (Box 54)
  June Adspac Retreat
- Project 2000! (Box 54)
  - Creating a Best Managed University (version 1.0), 1995-12
  - Foils by Fred Rogers with Budgets, Costs, etc, 1995-11
  - IBM Systems Integration Proposal, 1996-01
- ADSPAC - Minutes and Handouts, 1996-06-1996-12 (Box 54)
  Notable Projects: University Procurement Card; Common Address
- CIT Welcome Back Packs (NetID, Bear Access, Network Services), 1993 (Box 54)
- EZ-Remote - Forms, explanations, MacSLIP info, 1992 (Box 54)
- Bear Access Guide for the Macintosh, 1993-08 (Box 54)
- Bear Essentials and CIT News about Bear Access, 1993-02 (Box 54)
- SMTP Description - Postel, 1982 (Box 55)
- DIRTS - APS Department Info and Resource Tracking System, 1987 (Box 55)
- IBM 3191 Display Station, User's Guide, 2nd edition, 1987-01 (Box 55)
- Financial Information System Working Group, 1988 (Box 55)
  Surveys, Meetings, Results
- Emails - IR Organization, Exemplar, Caucas, 1994-1995 (Box 55)
- Emails - IR Miscellaneous Technologies, 1994-1996 (Box 55)
- Apple MAC LAN Stuff - Appletalk, Farallon Hubs, 1980-1989 (Box 55)
- MAC IS Managing Apple Computers in Information Systems, 1989-1990 (Box 55)
- CIT Sales - Product Catalog, 1992 (Box 55)
- JW Rudan Meeting Notebooks (2), 1985-1995 (Box 55)
- JW Rudan Telephone Logs (5), 1986-1997 (Box 55)
- Miscellaneous Topics - email copies, old saved copies, 1990-1999 (Box 55)
- Emails - EPOCH, Mass Storage, NSSF, 1993-1995 (Box 55)
- Explanation of DIAL access (Rick Jones), 1991 (Box 55)
- Hamilton College - OSS Project to Eliminate Use of SPIRES, 1990 (Box 55)
- OSS - Office Support Systems - Startup, Cost Recovery and Overheads re organization, projects, etc, 1989-1990 (Box 55)
- CIT Hiring Procedures - Forms, Policy, 1992 (Box 55)
- IR Project Leader Training and other Workshops, 1990 (Box 55)
  Application Development Methodology by Thomann
- CASE - Computer Aided Software Engineering - Natural Architect and use in designing SMA, 1990 (Box 55)
- SMA - Security Maintenance and Administration for Adabas, 1990-1993 (Box 55)
- CIT Software Lending Library, Contracts and License Agreements - Policy and MS-DOS, Mac Holdings, 1990 (Box 55)
- Software AG materials - ENTIRE Function Server and Intro to Object Orientation and Product Set, 1992 (Box 55)
- Client Tracking Systems ( Information Management Tracking System Proposal, Tracking System Work Group Minutes, Distributed Client Tracking Architecture by Hanushevsky, 1991 (Box 55)
- EDP Audit Items - Glenn Mueller, Auditor, 1991 (Box 55)
- CUDA - Newsletters, User Group Meeting, Specs for Payroll/Personnel, 1991 (Box 55)
- Project Development Plan, System Specs - Preventative Maintenance System, 1994 (Box 55)
- Desktop Platform Specs for P2K PeopleSoft systems, 1996 (Box 55)
- P2K - Legacy Support Unit, 1996 (Box 55)
- Cornell University - Reaffirmation of Accreditation, 1992 (Box 55)
  Middle States Association, Commission on Higher Education
- CIT Security Alerts, 1989-1993 (Box 55)
- Claris - Technical Solutions for the Macintosh, 1989-09 (Box 55)
- History of Computing CD-ROM An Encyclopedia of the People and Machines that Made Computer History (Mark Greenia) (Box 55)
- Cornell - The Big Picture -Outline of Presentation for CU Employees on IT at Cornell by John W. Rudan with an assortment of handouts and materials., 2001 (Box 55)
- Bear Access Users Guide, Bear Essentials, and Policy Handouts., 1993 (Box 55)
- CIT Policies and Procedures Manual, 1991 (Box 55)
- Cornell and the Age of Technology - VP Lambert to Assemblies Fall Retreat, 1996-09 (Box 55)
- CIT Policies and Procedures Manual (2 file folders), 1991 (Box 55)
- Polley McClure - Miscellaneous Stuff, 1999 (Box 55)
- Is Your Software Legal, 1999 (Box 55)
- Executive Oversight Group (EOG) Project 2000, 2000 (Box 55)
- Publications, Periodicals, Magazines and Magazine Articles
- The Cornell Engineer (Box 56)
  - The Cornell Computing Center completing its first year, 1954-12
  - Engineering Cornell Quarterly Vol. 8, No. 3, 1973-10
    The Science of Information (Computer Science theme)
  - Contents Theme - Advanced Computing including Project Ezra, Optical Computing, Biochips, 1987-02-1987-03
  - A History of Data Processing at Cornell by Larry F. Baum - draft of article For Nov 1967 Issue with corrections by J.W.Rudan, 1967
  - Engineering Cornell Quarterly Vol. 21, No. 2, 1986-1987
- Assorted Publications on Computing at Cornell (Box 56)
  - MicroVAX systems Facilitate Energy Management and Control Cornell University (H Michael Newman)
  - Cornell University by Barbara Call, PC Week, 1985
  - Enormous Changes in Scholarly Publishing Expected as a Result of Advances in Information Technology - Chronicle of Higher Ed (M. Stuart Lynn), 1990-11
  - The Untold Story of how the Internet Forced Bill Gates to reverse his Corporate Stategy by Kathy Rebello, Business Week, 1996-07
    (references Steven Sinofsky visit to Cornell in 2/94 and seeing Bear Access)
  - Cornell Infobase - Online Info in the year 2000 about Cornell IT
  - edu Magazine - The Education Magazine of Digital Equipment Corporation Cornell University's Project Socrates - Issue No. 46, 1987-1988
  - MicroVAX Systems Manage Energy Resources at Cornell University Issue No. 49 with Timeline and other supplemental Information about BACNet protocols by H. Michael Newman, 1988-1989
  - Apple Macintosh Publications
    Big Machine on Campus - Chris Pelkie about Apple's Desktop Publishing System at Cornell - 1987. Apple University Arts - Online Time Cards; A New Way to "Punch In" at Cornell. (v 1, # 1) Winter 1998
  - IBM Publications
    The Computer Age, The Evolution of IBM Computers DPD Digest - May 1976 - To computer - and Holmes, it's Elementary Chuck Brucken, Marketing Rep on PBM development
  - Application Brief - NSF Supercomputer Center based on IBM Mainframe And attached Processors (at Cornell University), 1986-12
  - Application Brief - Computers Emerge as Important New Human Resource Management Tools (at Cornell University), 1987-12
  - Application Brief - IBM 4381 Mainframe Computer Advances Social Science Research (at Cornell University), 1987-10
  - Newsline Software Products - ADSM: A backup Solution for Cornell University, 1995-07
- EDUCOM/EDUCAUSE Publications (Box 56)
  - Beyond Megaflops: The Cornell National Supercomputing Facility by Lawrence A. Lee, Educom Review, 1989
  - CAUSE/EFFECT Campus Profile, Cornell University, 1996
  - Educom Review; Networking/Internet/Telecom Act, 1999-11-1999-12
  - Educause Review; Then, Now, and Tomorrow - Technology's Transformation Of Higher Education, 2000-01-2000-02
  - The Joe Wyatt Challenge - 101 Success Stories of Information Technologies In Higher Education.., 1991
    includes 8 CU Successes
- CORNELL Publications (Box 56)
  - Report to Associates, A Program for the Advancement of Industry, Business and Higher Education - Cornell Computing Center Opens, 1954-01
  - The Cornell Computing Center - Information Bulletin, 1963
  - Cornell Alumni News - The Computer "Thinks" for Many - article about the Cornell Computing Center, 1960-12
  - Cornell Reports - James Scannell: A Man in Search of a System All about Cornell Admissions by Scannell the Dean, 1981-03
  - Cornell Countryman - The Computer Age at Cornell by Kristen M. Miller, 1989-12
- Cornell University Research Reports (Box 56)
  - Research at Cornell Electronic Computers make Maps from Photographs - Arthur J. McNair, 1955-1956
  - Research at Cornell - Cornell Computing Center Lesser and Rosenblatt at the B220 console., 1959-1960
  - Cornell University Industry Research Park - as there is Reference to the 370/168 at Langmuir Lab., 1970-1979
- Software AG, 1994 (Box 56)
  Connecting the Theoretical and the Practical: Cornell University Implements Open Systems Computing
- Facilities Inventory Materials (Box 56)
  - Cornell Facilities Inventory System: A Guide, Vol. 1, 1970
    Ira B. Nadel, Office of Institutional Studies, Cornell
  - Higher Education - Facilities Inventory and Classification Manual HEW # (OE) 74-11424, 1973
  - Standard Location Designations - Cornell Facilities Noel Desch, Director B and P, to DDDH list, 1974-09
  - SUNY Facilities Inventory Procedures, 1972
  - SUNY Space Reporting - Barbara Friedman, APS, 1984-06
  - Guide to the Capital Projects Tracking System (Gita Fonarov and Deborah MacInnes), 1985-10
  - Space Costing: Who should Pay for the Use of College Space, 1977
    Published by the Education Facilities Laboratories
  - The Facilities Inventory; Managing for Conservation, 1980-06
    Steven Carr, Facilities Coordinator to 67th Conference
- Project Development Plan for the Utilities Data System (Ron Parks, Diane Duthie, Patricia Welch), 1985-04 (Box 56)
- Documentation for the APS Activity Reporting System (ARS), 1985-10 (Box 56)
- Cornell Use of Natural and ADABAS User Exits (Tom Dimock), 1994-07
- Computer Security at Cornell; Report and Executive Summary (Coopers and Lybrand ) (Box 56)
- Project Mandarin Materials (Box 56)
  - Project Mandarin Quarterly Review, 1991-09
  - Project Mandarin (prospectus), 1993-12
  - Workshop Presentations, 1994-01
  - Probemaker Reference Guide, 1994-01
  - Project Mandarin Consortium Promo Booklet, 1994-11
    (Excellent Summary of Activity, Institutions, Implementations)
  - Programmers Guide - Student Jobs and Internships, 1995-10
  - Project Mandarin SideCar, 1996-04
  - Cornell University Student and Staff Directories Production, 1978-05
    Current systems, Improvements, and Alternate Means of Production - Robert J Blinken '78 OR 519 Project Report
- Old IBM and other Reference Manuals contributed by Tom Dimock (Box 56)
  - IBM Operators Guide (CCC copy - for different card machines), 1959-07
  - 101 Electronic Statistical Machine, 1958
  - IBM 407 Accounting Machine
  - IBM System 370 Reference Manuals, 1980-1989
  - IBM 3270 Information Display System - Reference Summary
  - Adabas Programmer's Reference Data - Software AG, 1980
  - Introduction to VITAL - Designing Information Systems for the 1990s - Apple Computer, 1992
  - Using Finite Automata as a programming technique (Tom Dimock ), 1980-1989
  - Ithaca High School Computing Courses using Cornell computing, 1966-1967
  - IBM Systems Journal - cover has picture from "Bells and Whistles" film created at the Cornell National Supercomputing Facility, 1990
  - Boardwatch Magazine on CU-SeeMe - cover and article 1994, 1994-06
- Educom Publications (Box 56)
  - Educom Bulletin - Special Issue on Financial Planning Models, 1982-10
    Benefits, Directions, Alternatives (Daniel A Updegrove)
  - Educom Networking Publication - An information Service for the Global Academic Networking Community, 1986
- Theory Center - Annual Report to the Provost, 1986-1987 (Box 56)
- Theory Center - 1988 Program Plan, 1987-07 (Box 56)
- Theory Center -Six Year Renewal Proposal to the National Science Foundation, 1988-05 (Box 56)
- Theory Center -Program Plans and Funding Requests, 1987-1988 (Box 56)
- Bear Access Project Team (Box 56)
  - Interview Training - Mission and Goals, 1994
  - Interview Training - Toolkit #1 to #16, 1994
  - Interview Training - Toolkit #17 to #31, 1994
  - Road Maps - Expressway and Detailed Directions to the Internet, 1994
- Project 2000 - Solicitations for Support Funding, 1995 (Box 57)
- P2K - Anonymous Letters and Responses, 1998 (Box 57)
- P2K - Press Articles (Yale also) and Informix, 1998-1999 (Box 57)
- Hein Online and NDSL, 1990-2000 (Box 57)
- Information Technology Officers Organization (at CU), 1990-2000 (Box 57)
- Student and Academic Information Services, 1997 (Box 57)
  Mission, Vision, and Reengineering Prospective
- Coding Forms (Box 57)
  - Wiring Collate for the 360/20.
  - OCS Coding Form (generic) for keypunching
  - IBM Fortran Coding Form
- Project 2000 - Communication Plans, Strategies (from Cecilia Cowles), 1996 (Box 57)
- Project 2000 Reports 1) creating a best managed university, and 2) Focus Group Research, 1996 (Box 57)
- Project 2000 - Communication Team Deliberations, etc (from C Cowles), 1996 (Box 57)
- Project 2000 - HR/Payroll system reports, 1996 (Box 57)
- Presentation/papers by F. A. Rogers related to P2K, 1996 (Box 57)
  The Pressures on Higher Education Today (Powerpoint foils) Campus-Wide Approach to Systems Planning
- Computing at Columbia (University) Timeline - Printed Copy as of 7/3/03 Updates at http://www.columbia.edu/acis/history/index.html (Box 57)
- Project 2000!: Creating a Best-Managed University - version 1.0, 1995-12 (Box 57)
- Project 2000 - Announcing Jack Freeman as Exec Director (Box 57)
- Project 2000 - Alumni Affairs/Development Staff Briefing, 1997 (Box 57)
- Project 2000 - Shared Vision Documents, 1997-04 (Box 57)
- Project 2000 - Survey - Perceptions on Admin Processes and Readiness, 1997 (Box 57)
  Perceptions of Cornell Administrative Processes and Campus Readiness for Change (Survey conducted in 12/77; report March 1998)
- COLTS - Cornell On-Line Time Cards (PR from Apple), 1998 (Box 57)
- Network Resources Re-organize (also JGSM report on services), 1992 (Box 57)
- An Analysis of the Accounting Data Warehouse System at Cornell A Report by 3 students in NBA 641, Logistics and Manufacturing Strategy, 1998 (Box 57)
- Interactive Media Center - Startup, Reports, Proposals and Grants, 1987-1989 (Box 57)
- CIT - A Perspective for Employees, 1990 (Box 57)
  An Excellent Introduction to the new and changing CIT
- A Practical Guide to PL/I for Business Applications Programmers, 1983 (Box 57)
- Innovations in Academic Computing - Project Ezra at Cornell, 1985-1988 (Box 57)
  Sponsored by IBM Advanced Education Program (AEP). 2 folders
- System Operations Manual - copy belonging to Joseph A. Maio
- Reports and documents primarily referenced for the writing of the History of Computing at Cornell. Organized by decade.
- Signed copy of "The History of Computing at Cornell University", with correspondence with Hunter Rawlings, 2005 (Box 58)
- 1950s and earlier
- Animal Husbandry at Cornell University Kenneth L Turk, 1986 (Box 58)
  A History and Record of Development from 1868 to 1963 The section on Automated Data Processing starts on page 162. Includes letters from Wilmot Carter and J. D. Burke responding to S. R. Searle's request for supplementary information, and An original and retyped copy (for including in electronic media) of the History of the Northeast Dairy Records Processing Laboratory by Lyle Wadell
- Present Status of the Cornell Computing Center (R. J Walker), 1953-10 (Box 58)
  Report to the Advisory Committee Includes discussion of DISAC, a machine to be built by Rosenblatt? Also a note from Lesser and Walker to "Anyone Interested in Machine Computation" all about the CPC
- Dom Bordonaro's Papers-Miscellaneous Talks Delivered, 1940-1980 (Box 58)
- An Analysis of Data Processing and Computing at Cornell University (W. S Gere, B. McK. Johnson, R. C. Morris), 1967 (Box 58)
  With original letter to T. P Wright and comments by Irene Van Zile and Hank Vaughan (2 copies, original and another)
- An Introduction to coding the Burroughs 220 (xerox copy), 1958-12 (Box 58)
- IBM 24 Card Punch 26 Printing Card Punch - Manual of Operations, 1958 (Box 58)
- Cornell Computing Center - Annual Report, 1956-1957 (Box 58)
- Materials from Industrial Engineering Dept. Annual Reports (A. Schultz, Dept Head ), 1955 (Box 58)
- Computing Center Publicity, etc, 1950-1959 (Box 58)
  Old pictures, articles, clippings
- 1960
- Guides to the Use of Facilities at the Cornell Computing Center, 1964-1966 (Box 58)
- Staff/Student Employees at the Cornell Computing Center, 1961-1966 (Box 58)
- 1604 Computer Selection and Supporting Materials including Kissoff of other vendors; Formal report, "Report of the Technical Committee on the Purchase of a Large Computing Machine", 1961 (Box 58)
- Merry Christmas Banner, 1960-1969 (Box 58)
- Pictures from the 1960s and Cornell Computing Center Publicity Pub, 1960-1969 (Box 58)
- Operating Summaries - CDC 1604, 1962-1965 (Box 58)
- Research Use Statistics - CDC 1604 and B220, 1960-1965 (Box 58)
- Peterson/McWilliams - Payroll/Accounting System Issues, 1969 (Box 58)
- Peterson, A. H. - Correspondence on Computing Issues, etc, 1968-1969 (Box 58)
  Mostly on the proposed SBO 360/25 for the accounting system
- OCS Reports by R. W Conway and other Technical, Operating and Personnel Issues of the time Technical Report - the Cornell-HASP System for the IBM 360 by Conway and Worley (in part the COOL specs), 1966-1969 (Box 58)
- Setting up OCS - Long and Conway memos, etc, 1966 (Box 58)
- Proposals to NSF to support acquisition of computer (histories) (Box 58)
  - Control Data 1604, 1961
  - IBM 360/67, 1966
- Miscellaneous Memos, Rates, Staff, Org Charts, CLASP Issues, 1960-1969 (Box 58)
- OCS Reports by Erik McWilliams (Formation of ACAB), 1969-1970 (Box 58)
- OCS Director's Meetings 1968-69 (McWilliams mostly), 1968-1969 (Box 58)
- OCS Directors Meetings and Agendas, 1969-1970 (Box 58)
- OCS Grapevine by McWilliams mostly and Rudan, 1969-71 (Box 58)
- 360/67 Costs and Committee Report recommending its acquisition, 1965-1966 (Box 58)
- Walsh Committee Report (joint study with IBM) on Administrative Information System for Cornell and earlier Conway/Rudan/Saltzman"fairly comprehensive plan for data processing" at CU, 1965 (Box 58)
- FLCCC - Finger Lakes Colleges Computing Center - correspondence, etc, 1966 -1967 (Box 58)
  Including copy of proposal to NSF
- FLARCO - Annual Reports, 1st and 2nd by Arlene Larsen, 1969-1970 (Box 58)
  FLARCO -Finger Lakes Regional Computing Organization 1st report by Saltzman/Larsen, 2nd by McWilliams/Larsen
- Perpendicular Intersections with a DiPole Field (David H. Bessel ), 1960 (Box 58)
- Cornell University Libraries Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 58)
  Installation of Automated Acquisitions and In process Control
- Control Data 1604, Programming Manual (copy of Dave Bessel's), 1962 (Box 58)
- 1970s
- Annual Reports 1970-71 to 1977-78 by Rudan and Blackmun, 1970-1979
  Includes detailed reports by APS staff to Hollenbeck in1978
- The Crisis and Challenge of Administrative Computing at, 1971-03
  Cornell University - report by Henry G. Vaughan
- The Future of Administrative Computing at CU ( Judy Campbell ), 1973
- McWilliams to Rudan Transition exchanges with S A Lawrence, 1969-1970 (Box 59)
  Includes a copy of "The Crisis of 1969" from the Cornell Chronicle published in 1989, and F A Long on the "Death of The Cornell Computing Center."
- Miscellaneous Technical/Service Reports (IT for Instructors), 1970-1980 (Box 59)
- Miscellaneous Report (Blackmun, Rudan, Lawrence ), 1975-1979 (Box 59)
  Planning, Cost Cutting, Statement of Objectives and Results
- Interactive Computing Items and proposals/documents, 1975-1979 (Box 59)
- Computing Advisory Council notes, 1971 (Box 59)
- Campus Computer Survey, 1971,1973,1978 (Box 59)
- Does Every Campus Need a Computer? The Ford Foundation, 1971 (Box 59)
- MSA - Recommendation to Purchase Mark IV, 1972 (Box 59)
- Evaluation of CU's new SIS by Dave Freeman of Ketron, Inc, 1973 (Box 59)
- Recommendation to Increase Computing Capacity - UCB, 1973 (Box 59)
  And Report by Faculty Committee on the UCB Report (Chester, chair)
- 168 Task Force (for installation) and Binghamton/CU Consortium, 1974 (Box 59)
- Minicomputers and OCS - Policy and Relationship by Dave Bessel, 1974 (Box 59)
- OCS Office of Computer Services Newsletter, 1970-1974 (Box 59)
- DeBoer Report, 1975 (Box 59)
- Use of the Computer at Cornell - 1975 Committee Report, 1975 (Box 59)
  G. V. Chester et al (Chester, Thomas Report) 2 copies
- Notes from meeting with SAL, JWR and President Corson, 1975-05 (Box 59)
- UCB Deliberations, 1976-1979 (Box 59)
- PLATO Miscellaneous Documents, 1976 to 1980-1982 (Box 59)
- History of OCS by Cecilia (Uren) Cowles (timelines, statistics, machines), 1977 (Box 59)
- Wizard of OCKS - A Fairy Tale - Instigated and Edited by Chuck, 1977 (Box 59)
  Boeheim with a Historical Perspective by Rich Gallagher
- Planning Reports, 1978 (Box 59)
  Comments on Cornell Planning for Computing - James Emery of Educom And Bruce Arden from Michigan Instructional Computing Comparison by Blackmun and Van Houweling
- Word Processing/Office Automation (General Services), 1978 (Box 59)
  (Sample Survey on Automated Office Equipment; Not results)
- Blackmun to Rudan assuming acting Director of OCS; notes/issues, 1979 (Box 59)
- Transition Documents (mostly financial) - Blackmun-Rudan-King, 1978-1980 (Box 59)
- Use of EFPM for Budget Planning by J W Rudan, 1979-1980 (Box 59)
- Upgrade/Modernize CU Data Networks Proposal, 1978 (Box 59)
- CUMC Incidental items and reports, 1975-1979 (Box 59)
  Including materials from SAL and UCB
- Report of the Visiting Committee on Computing, 1979-1980 (Box 59)
- Institutional Planning and Analysis (IPA) Annual Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 59)
- 1970 Leftovers - Misc. stuff (IT reports, theft of service, campus terminals), 1970-1979 (Box 59)
- 1970s Feedback, correspondence, email clarifications, etc, 1970-1979 (Box 59)
- 1970 Misc. Reports: Student Interactive Computing. Social, 1970-1979 (Box 59)
  Science Computing, UCB stuff, PLATO, etc
- 1970 Highlights - OCS Bulletins, Annual Report Summaries, 1970-1979 (Box 59)
  CompSci Annual Reports, Cornell Chronicle articles UCB Files and other Key documents
- Cornell Chronicle - copies of articles re computing, 1970-1979 (Box 59)
- 1980-1989
- CCS/CIT Bulletins, Announcements, Guides, etc, 1980 (Box 59)
- Critical Computing Needs - UCB Recommendations to Provost, 1980-02 (Box 59)
- Planning Documents by Ken King, 1981-1984 (Box 59)
  - Computer Services Unit Plan, 1981-09
  - Long Range Direction for Computing, 1984-03
- Comm and Text Systems; Word Processing Equipment Selection (King and Cogger), 1981 (Box 59)
- APS Staff Allocations, Income, Rudan as Acting, 1981 (Box 59)
- Nibbles (on microcomputing) Decentralized Acad Computing - DACS, 1981 (Box 59)
- Accounting System Feasibility Study (Peat, Marwick, Mitchell, 1981 (Box 59)
- Upgrade of Financial Accounting System (J. S. Ostrom), 1982 (Box 59)
- Using the IBM Computer at CU - Introductory Guide-Trochim/Kirk, 1982 (Box 59)
- Future Directions for Administrative Computing, 1983-12 (Box 59)